Guide to the Llewellyn Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile
  - Box 3, folder 110 (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Box 3, folder 118 (Box 9, Folder 241)